Guide to the Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Innovative Academic Courses, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1992-086
  - SWOP 116: Equal Protection Law: From Brown to Bakke: Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 120AB: Working Effectively With Disturbed Children, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 121: Experience-Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - SWOP 122: Children's Health Council: Teaching Learning Handicapped Children, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 123: Life in a Wheelchair, Winter 80 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 125: Access for the Physically Handicapped, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Access for the Physically Handicapped, Winter 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 126: Therapeutic Recreation for the Developmentally Disabled, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 132; Solid Waste Management: A Conservationist Approach, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 133: Appropriate Technology, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 142 South Africa and the US Investment: Struggle for Justice, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - 143: Who are the Palestinians?, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 144: Decision Making in International Affairs, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 153: The Politics of Solar Engery, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 169: Whales and Whaling: Politics and Actions, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 170: The Politics of Women's Reproductive Health, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 173A: Domestic Violence, Myth and Reality, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - SWOP 177 Feminism: What Are We Fighting For?, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 186: The Juvenile Justice System, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 198: Ethical Issues in Business, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 103: An Oral Traditions Approach to Research on Ethnic Minorities, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 111: Mexican and Chicano Public Art, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - SWOP 114: Work and Vocation, A Fresh Look, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - SWOP 115: Conscription, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - SWOP 120AB: Working Effectively With Disturbed Children, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - SWOP 121: Experience Based Study of the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - SWOP 122: Children's Health Council: Teaching Learning Handicapped, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - SWOP 125: Access for the Physically Handicapped, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - SWOP 126B: Recreation for the Disabled, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - SWOP 129: Respecting the Child in a Changing Society, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - SWOP 131: The Automobile: Society's Challenge, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - SWOP 136: Working Towards an Environmentally Sustainable Soceity, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - SWOP 146: Zionism, Historical and Cultural Overview, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - SWOP 148: International Hunger and the American Response, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - SWOP 150: San Franciso Bay: Pollution and Biological Impacts, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - SWOP 152: Environment, technology and Culture in Japan, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - SWOP 178: Feminist Theology, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - SWOP 184: Asian Americans in a Contemporary Urban Setting, Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - SWOP 198: Ethical Issues in Business: Spring 1980 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - SWOP 115: Conscription, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - SWOP 120A Working Effectively With Disturbed Children, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - SWOP 121: The Experience Based Study in the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - SWOP 122: Children's Health Council: Teaching Children Who Have Failed, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - SWOP 126: Theraputic Recreation for the Developmentally Disabled, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - SWOP 129: Respecting the Child in a Changing Society, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - SWOP 145: Third World Media and Reality, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - SWOP 151: Politics of Energy, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - SWOP 155: Space for the Future, postponed, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - SWOP 155: Space for the Future, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - SWOP 162: Bicycle Safety, Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Rape Ed. Postponed to Winter (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - SWOP 181: Asian American Literature Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - SWOP 187: Education and Ethnicity: Toward a Theory of Cultural Diversity- Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - SWOP 198: Ethical Issues in Business- Fall 1980 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - SWOP 104: Oral Histories of Political Women: 1920-1980, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 118: Minorities: A Legal Perspective, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - SWOP 120A: Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 121: Experience Based Study of the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 122: CHC: Teaching Children Who Have Failed, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 126: Ther. Rec. For Dev. Disabled, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 132: Waste: Resource or Problem?, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - SWOP 148: Internaational Hunger and US Aid, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - SWOP 155: Our Future in Space, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 160: Self-Identification, Self-Exploration, Social Act. (not approved) Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 162: Bicy. Safety at Stanford, Strat. for Change Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 173: Domestic Violence, Working with Battered Women, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 198: Corp. Resp. and Ind. Bus. Ethics, Winter 1981 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 120AB Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 121: Experience Based Study of Meaning of Being Handicapped, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 127: Cultural Content on Children's Books and Games, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 135: California Water: History and Politics Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 150: San Fransisco Bay: Pollution and Biological Impacts, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 150: San Fransisco Bay Action Project, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Projects SWOP 150, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - 155: Space for the Future (cancelled, not approved) Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 165: Men's Lives: An Examination of Male Roles, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 168: Democratic Socialism: Theory and Practice, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 177: What are We Fighting for: A Closer Looks at Feminism, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 180: Chicano Ideology and Biculturalism: A Synthesis of Concepts, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 185: Minority Issues In Higher Education, Spring 1981 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 120A Working Effectively With Disturbed Children, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 121 Experience Based Study of the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 137 Environmental Conflict Resolution Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - SWOP 148 International Hunger and US Aid, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 151 The Politics of Energy, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 161 Animal Rights: Issues and Politics, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - SWOP 173 Domestic Violence: Working with Battered Women, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 176 Women in the Labor Force: Issues and Organizing, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 180 Refugee Resettlement in the US, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 182 Chicano Lives: Race and Class in the Southwest, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 183 The Central American Crisis: Political-Econmic Origins and US Policy, Fall 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 120AB Working Effectively With Disturbed Children, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 121 Experience-Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 130 Political and Economic Realities of Smaller Daily Newspapers, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 148 World Hunger and US Aid, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 157 The Nuclear Arms Race: Why Don't We Have Better Options? Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - SWOP 159 The Bomb Next Door: Nuclear Weapons Proliferation in the Bay Area, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 168 Democratic Socialism: Theory and Practice, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 170 Strategies Of Radical Social Change, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 175 Women and Science, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 177 Off Our Backs: Introduction to Feminist Studies, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - SWOP 184 The Social Role of Children's Theatre, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - SWOP 186 The African Influence of Western Culture, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - SWOP 188 Asian Americans: Perpectives Through Generations, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - SWOP 198 Corporate Responsibility and Individual Business Ethics, Winter 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - SWOP Introduction to Chicano Politics, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - SWOP 104 Oral Histories of Women Peace Activists, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - SWOP 110 Black Media Workshop, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - SWOP 120AB Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - SWOP 121 Experience-Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - SWOP 129 Respecting The Child in a Changing Society, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - SWOP 135 Biological Issues in Environmental Policy, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - SWOP 139 Ecology and Economics, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - SWOP 140 Black Mural Composition, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - SWOP 150 San Fransisco Bay: Pollution and Biological Impacts, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - SWOP 153 High School Dropouts: Facts and Fallacies, Spring 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - SWOP 155 Urban Plunge: Poverty and the Catholic Church's Response, Spring 1982 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - SWOP 157 The Nuclear Arms Race: Why Aren't There Better Solutions? Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 159 The Bomb Next Door: Nuclear Proliferation In the Bay Area Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - SWOP 169 Gay History/Gay Heritage: A Critical Introduction Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 171 Men in Difficult Times Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 174 Issues in Self-Defence For Women Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 177 Exploring Views of Women: An Introduction to Feminism Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 178 Two Women Eye to Eye: Lebian Visions in Literature Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - SWOP 179 Chicana Women Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - SWOP 181 Pornography: Are We Being Raped? Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 185 Minority Issues in Higher Education Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 190 Cultural Democracy In the Classroom Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 195 The Minority Porfessional Dual Commitment Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 198 Corporate Responsibility and Individual Business Ethics Spring 1982 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 107 The Baby Boom Going Gray: Support Systems for the Elderly, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 141 Student Involvment in Stanford Governance, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - SWOP Ending World Hunger, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 151 The Politics of Energy, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 153 High School Dropouts: Facts and Fallacies, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 159: The Bomb Next Door Nuclear Weapons Proliferation in the BA, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 182 Chicano Lives: Race and Class in The Southwest, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - SWOP 183 Central America in Crisis, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 186 The African Origins of Humanity, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 192 Political Campaigns and the American Voter, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 112 Art and Society Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 139 Ecology and Economics Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 145 Jewish Women: Some Jewish Feminist Perspectives Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 163- Radical Analysis of American Society Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 198 Buornia Ethics, Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 171 A Study of Marixm and Social Class Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - SWOP 174 Issues in Self-defence for Women Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 175 Current Feminist Issues Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 184 Democracy and Military Government in Latin America, Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - SWOP 186B African Science, Technology and Religion, Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 187 Introduction to Asian American History and Issues Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 190 Cultural Democracy in the Classroom Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 198 Business Ethics and Corporate Resonsibility, Winter 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 107: Elderly (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 115 Community Development: Methods, Strategies, Action 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 120 Distrssed Children (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 120AB Disturbed Children (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 124 Video Games (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - SWOP 136 Endangered Species: Strategies for Preservation 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 144 Zionism, Isreal and Palestine 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 146 Women of the New Rig (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 158 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 165 Men's Lives (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 16 Gay History (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - SWOP 171 A Study of Marx and Marxism 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 174 Self-Defence (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 178 Literature Workshop (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 184- Democracy and Military Governments with Latino Americans (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 186-C Africans In Transistion (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - SWOP 194 Communism in the 1930's (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - SWOPSI 194, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 196- Social Representation (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 120A Working Effectively With Disturbed Children Fall 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 151A and SWOP 151B Politics of Energy Summer 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 121 Experience-Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped (Psyc) Fall 1982 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 135 Native American History Fall 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 139 Ecology and Economics Fall 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 177 Intro. to Feminism Spring 1983 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 120A Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Fall 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 135: Contemporary Indian Affiars, Fall 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 151 The Politics of Energy Fall 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 161 The Bomb: Disarmament, Stalemate or Holocaust? Fall 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - SWOP 174 Issues in Self Defense for Women, Fall 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 183 Central America in Crisis Fall 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 184 Democracy and Military Government in Latin America, Fall 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 186A Ancient African History: The Truth Revealed, Fall 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 111 Street Theatre, Cabaret and Brecht Winter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 120AB Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Winter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 123 The United Nations on Crisis Winter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 148 Ending Poverty and Hunger in Developing Countries, Winter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 160: Military Funding for Research at Stanford, Winter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - SWOP 161: The Bomb: Disarmament, Stalemate or Holocaust, Winter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 166: 1984 and George Orwell, Winter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 174: Issues in Self Defense for Women, Winter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - SWOP 185 Revolution In Latin America, Winter Quarter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 186B Afrikan Science, Technology, and Religion Winter Quarter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 190 Cultural Democracy in the Classroom Winter Quarter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 198 Corporate Responsibility and Business Ethics, Winter 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 120AB Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 133: American Indian Federal Law, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 134 The Paiute Indians of Pyramid Lake Spring 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 136 The Stanford Powwow Spring 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 139 Ecological Perspectived on Economics, Cancelled Spring 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 162: Democratic Theory for Activists, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - SWO P165 Men's Lives, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 167: Consiracy of Silence: the Trama of Incest, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 171: Women's Legal Issues, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 173 Feminism and Spirituality Spring 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - SWOP 174 Issues in Self-Defence for Women, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 175: Black Women's Literature, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 183: Central America in Crisis, Spring 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 198 Corporate Responsibility and Business Ethics Spring 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 174: Issues in Self Defense for Women, Summer 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - SWOP 183: Central America in Crisis, Summer 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - SWOP 120A Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 131 Who Owns the Media: Cable Communications and the Consumer, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 140: Insight into Futures, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 140, Reader, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 160: Military Funding for Research at Stanford, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 161: The Bomb, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 174: Issues in Self Defense for Women, Fall 1984;1985 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 182: Chicano Lives, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 183: Central America in Crisis, Fall Quarter 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 111 Drugs, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 120A, Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 143: The Consensus Process: Winter 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - SWOP 150 Land Use and Abuse Winter 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 174A Issues in Self Defense for Women, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 174(2) Issues in Self Defense for Women, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 190: Cultural Democracy in the Classroom, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 198: Comp. Resp., Winter 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 108 Alzheimers Disease Prject, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 120A Working Effecitvely with Disturbed Children, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 132: Solid Waste Manegement, A Conservationist's Approach, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 140: Approaching the 21st Century, Insights into Futures, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - SWOP 163: Taiwan and the China Issue, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 165: Men's Lives: Examining Male Roles and Masculinity, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 169: Demystifying Homosexuality, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - SWOP 171: Women's Legal Issues, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 172: Feminism. Spirituality and Social Justice, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 173: Race, Sex, and Class in Novels by Black Women, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 174: Issues in Self Defense for Women, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 178: Two Women Eye to Eye: Lesbian Visions in Literature, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 183: Central America in Crisis, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 187: Introduction to Asian American History and Issues, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 198: Corporate Responsibility and Business Ethics, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 112 Muralism as A Social Conscience Art, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 126 Health Care Inequities Fall and Winter 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - SWOP 139 An Ecological Economics Fall 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 142 Volunteers: Community Service in the 1980's, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 147 Hunger, Creating the Tools for Change, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 161 The Bomb, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 168 Politics of Gender and Sexuality, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 171 Women's Legal Issues Fall 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - SWOP Vietnam Remembered: The Asian Experinence, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 174 Issues on Self Defense for Women, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 183 Central America in Crisis, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 186 Vietnam: The American PER experience, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 187, Asian American History and Issues, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - SWOP 188 The Internationalization of Apartheid, Role of the US Fall 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - SWOP 109 Political Theater: The Living Newspaper Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 110 Street Theater and Brecht, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 139 Ecological Economies, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 162 Animal Rights and Research, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 163 Critique of Progressive Politics, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 174 Issues in Self Defense for Women, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 174B Adanced Issues in Self Defense, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 184 Advanced Topics on Central America, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 187B Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 187B Asian American Women, Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 198 Corporated Responsibility Winter 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 198, Winter 19851-986 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - SWOP 137, Pow Wow, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 163 Critique of Progressive Politics, Spring 1986 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 166 Men's Lives and Malcontenets, Spring 1986 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 170 Focus on the Black Athlete: Hero, Pawn, or Twentieth Century Gladiator? Spring 1986 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 172, Women and Ecology, Spring 1986 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 174 Self Defense for Women, Spring 1986 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 174B Intermediate Self Defense for Women, Spring 1986 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 176 Women and the Global Assembly Line, Spring 1986 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 197 High Cost of High Tech- Computer Citizenship, Spring 1986 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Men's Studies- Ted, Spring 1986 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 164 Men, Family Planning and Related Issues, Fall 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 138 American Indian Experience Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 32)